//Array of objects for easy game
let triviaGame = [
  {
    Question:
      "What NCAA Division I basketball team has the most national championships?",
    Correct: "UCLA",
    Answer: ["UCLA", "Tar Heels", "Indiana", "Uconn"],
  },
  {
    Question:
      "Who received the First Naismith College Coach of the Year Award?",
    Correct: "Coach Bobby Knight",
    Answer: [
      "Coach Bobby Knight",
      "Coach Tom Moore",
      "Coach Jim Boeheim",
      "Coach Jim Calhoun",
    ],
  },
  {
    Question:
      "The UCLA men hold the record for the most men's Division I NCAA chanpionships with 11. When did the UCLA men win their first basketball national championship?",
    Correct: "The was 1964",
    Answer: ["The was 1964", "It was 1965", "It was 1967", "It was 1989"],
  },
  {
    Question: "When was the first college basketball game played?",
    Correct: "January 18, 1896",
    Answer: [
      "January 18, 1896",
      "January 21, 1895",
      "February 14, 2013",
      "February 20, 1896",
    ],
  },
  {
    Question:
      " What school won the first NCAA Mens Basketball National Championships?",
    Correct: "Oregon in 1939",
    Answer: [
      "Oregon in 1939",
      "Uconn in 1950",
      " Kentucky in 1999",
      " Texas in 1943",
    ],
  },
  {
    Question: "What teams were in the Final Four back in 2000?",
    Correct: "Tar Heels, Michigan State, Florida Gators, Wisconsin",
    Answer: [
      "Tar Heels, Michigan State, Florida Gators, Wisconsin",
      "Uconn, Michigan State, Kentucky, Maryland",
      "Uconn, Maryland, UCLA, California -",
      "Michigan, Duke, Baylor, Eastern Ct State University -",
    ],
  },
  {
    Question:
      "What team won the National Championships in 2000 for Mens College Basketball",
    Correct: "Michigan State Spartans",
    Answer: [
      "Michigan State Spartans",
      "Kentucky Wildcats",
      "Eastern Warriors",
      "Golden State Warriors",
    ],
  },
  {
    Question:
      "What team won the National Championship in 1995 mens college basketball?",
    Correct: "UCLA Bruins",
    Answer: ["UCLA Bruins", "Louisville", "Wisconsin", "Hawaii"],
  },
  {
    Question:
      "Who was the Most Outstanding Player in the 1995 Mens College Basketball Championship?",
    Correct: "Ed O'Bannon - UCLA",
    Answer: [
      "Ed O'Bannon - UCLA",
      "Rex Chapmen - Kentucky",
      "Ray Allen - Uconn",
      "Ronnie Seikaly - Syracuse",
    ],
  },
  {
    Question:
      "The 1995 NBA draft picked two players from the North Carolina Tar Heels in the top 5, who are they?",
    Correct: "Jerry Stackhouse and Rasheed Wallace",
    Answer: [
      "Jerry Stackhouse and Rasheed Wallace",
      "Chris Webber and Jalen Rose",
      "Scott Burrell and Ray Allen",
      "Sherman Douglas and Derrick Coleman",
    ],
  },
  {
    Question:
      "He was drafted out of Syracuse University in 1990 as the number pick in the NBA draft, who is he?",
    Correct: "Derrick Coleman",
    Answer: [
      "Derrick Coleman",
      "Billy Owens",
      "Stephen Thompson",
      "Sherman Douglas",
    ],
  },
  {
    Question:
      "Syracuse University had a point guard that went by the name of the - General, who is he?",
    Correct: "Sherman Douglas",
    Answer: ["Sherman Douglas", "Conrad McRae", "Dave Johnson", "Mickey Mouse"],
  },
  {
    Question:
      "In 1984, Georgetown led by Patrick Ewing, won their first National Championship. Which school did they defeat 84-75 in the championship Game?",
    Correct: "Houston - Phi Slamma Jamma",
    Answer: [
      "Houston - Phi Slamma Jamma",
      "Georgie Tech",
      "George Mason",
      "University of Milwuakee",
    ],
  },
  {
    Question:
      "In the 1992 East regional final, Christian Laettner hit the game winning basket from the top of the key with one second left to lift DUKE to a 104-103 win. What team was their opponent?",
    Correct: "Kentucky Wildcats",
    Answer: ["Kentucky Wildcats", "West Virginia", "Kansas", "Kansas State"],
  },
  {
    Question: "Who was the lose against North Carolina in 1993?",
    Correct: "East Caroline University",
    Answer: ["East Caroline University", "Austin Peay", "Rutgers", "Purdue"],
  },
  {
    Question:
      "1985 was the first year the NCAA tournament had a grand total of 64 teams. Villanova defeated Georgetown to become the first national championship of the new format. Who was the loser?",
    Correct: "Marshall",
    Answer: [
      "Marshall",
      "Ohio State",
      "North Carolina Central University",
      "Howard University",
    ],
  },
  {
    Question:
      "Kentucky was stunned by which all African American starting lineup team in the 1966 National Championship? Hint: a movie was made about this team. ",
    Correct: "Texas Western University",
    Answer: [
      "Texas Western University",
      "Alabama University",
      "Mississippi State",
      "Vanderbilt",
    ],
  },
  {
    Question:
      "Syracuse was the National Champions in 2003, Who was the most outstanding polayer?",
    Correct: "Carmelo Anthony",
    Answer: [
      "Carmelo Anthony",
      "Nick Collison",
      "Gerry McNamara",
      "Kirk Hinrich",
    ],
  },
  {
    Question:
      "The very first Final Four, played in 1939, was held in which midwestern city?",
    Correct: "Evanston, Illinois",
    Answer: [
      "Evanston, Illinois",
      "Waterbury, CT",
      "Milwaukee, WI",
      "Kansas City, MO",
    ],
  },
  {
    Question: "In 1993, Southern Univesity beat what #4 team?",
    Correct: "Georgia Teach",
    Answer: ["Georgia Teach", "Murray State", "St. Johns", "Butler University"],
  },
];
